Steven Lee

2D/3D ARTIST

Phone 852 67115740

E-mail <u>alokstevens@gmail.com</u>

Location Hong kong

Telegram https://t.me/Attwice

Summary

Passionate 3D and 2D artist with over 5 years of experience in 3D modeling, concept art, rigging, and animation. At Brushpic designed several 2D and 3D NFTs, product models and ensured project integration on a daily basis. At EOrange Technology Limited Built 3D computer-based modeling, 3D environment, and animation using high-end computer workstations, software and tools.

Professional profile

Creative artist with a recognized talent for conveying personalities, emotions, weight, and motion. Collaborates well with others to generate and execute ideas within tight deadlines. Earned a reputation for dedication, humor, intelligence, and going "above and beyond" to help team-mates.

Professional experience

2018-07 – 2019-08 **2D Artist**

Brushpics

- Created concept arts, sketches, and NFTs.
- Designed flyers, textures, ads, and cartoon style images.
- Created 2D textures from hand and captured images for real-time rendering.

2018-07 – 2019-08 **3D Artist**

EOrange Technology Limited

- Built 3D computer-based modeling and animation using high-end computer workstations, software and tools.
- Created animating environments, characters and other assets within 3D environment.
- Designed 3D environment by modeling, texturing, animation, scene staging, art direction and production management.
- Designed and modeled various environment and character assets, ensuring the completion of 15+ promptly with high quality and within deadlines.
- Illustrated assets, textured objects and designed multiple app icons and menu screens, resulting in a 505 increase in overall productivity.
- Created banners and worked on improving the whole 3D model's development process to increase quality, efficiency and reduce costs.

Education

2012 – 2016 Game Art Bachelor's Degree
University of Honk Kong

Skills

Adobe: Photoshop, Illustrator, InDesign, After Effects	••••
3D Software: Maya, 3D Studio Max, Revit	••••
Modeling	••••
Rigging	••••
Animation	••••
Collaboration	
Open-Mindedness	••••
Project Management	••••